Finding Aid for Extension Service (University of Michigan) records, 1911-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Director's Office Files
  - Topical Files 1912-1959
    - Labor Institute 1932 (Box 13)
    - Lectures 1932-1959 (Box 13)
    - Legislative Material 1958-1959 (Box 13)
    - Library Extension 1917-1918 (Box 13)
    - Liverwright, A.A., Liberal Education 1958-1959 (Box 13)
    - Lurie, Nancy O., Anthropology 1957-1958 (Box 13)
    - Meally, John (Port Huron) 1937-1949 (Box 13)
    - Menton, Stoyan 1952 (Box 13)
    - Michigan Conference on Aging 1952 (Box 13)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents
      - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Minutes
        - 1953-1954 (Box 13)
        - 1954-1957 (Box 13)
      - Policies Adopted 1959 (Box 13)
      - Preliminary Report: Field and Extension Services 1954 (Box 13)
      - Report: Field and Extension Services of the State-Supported Institutions of Higher Learning in Michigan 1955 (Box 13)
      - Report: Study Committee on Field and Extension Services 1954 (Box 13)
      - Reports: Miscellaneous 1953-1955, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - Subcommittee on Conferences and Consultative School Services 1958 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Council on Adult Education-College Field Service Committee
      - Annual Report 1955/1956- 1957-1958 (Box 14)
      - Cooperative Extension Activities (U of M) with Other Michigan Colleges 1958 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence
        - 1945-1947 (Box 14)
        - 1948-1951 (Box 14)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 14)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 14)
      - Minutes
        - 1948-1954 (Box 14)
        - 1955-1959 (Box 14)
      - Proposal for a Cooperative Program of Field Services (Box 14)
      - Public Affairs Discussion Programs 1955-1956 (Box 14)
      - Southwest Michigan Cooperative Education Program 1955-1956 (Box 14)
      - Subcommittee on Economic Education Programs 1954-1956 (Box 14)
      - Subcommittee on Educational Programs with the Armed Forces 1956 (Box 14)
      - Subcommittee on Policies and Practices 1955-1956 (Box 14)
      - Subcommittee on Junior College-Four Year College Relationships 1954-1955, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Survey of Field Services, Policies, and Practices 1951-1952 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Council on Women in Business and Industry 1948-1954
      - Charter and Constitution (Box 14)
      - Correspondence (Box 14)
      - Minutes (Box 14)
      - Reports (Box 14)
    - Michigan Department of Public Instruction: Committee for Business Education 1946-1956 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Education Association: Advisory Committee on the Intermediate Unit 1955-1956 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Joint Committee on Health Education: Dr. Burton R. Corbus 1921-1941
      - Correspondence and Reports
        - 1936-1938 (Box 14)
        - 1938-1940 (Box 14)
        - 1940-1943 (Box 14)
      - Minutes, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Michigan Society of Gerontology 1956-1958 (Box 15)
    - Michigan Week
      - 1955-1956 (Box 15)
      - 1957-1959 (Box 15)
    - Midwest Seminar on American Foreign Policy
      - Third Midwest Seminar 1956 Madison, Wisconsin
        - General Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Participant's Evaluations (Box 15)
      - Fourth Midwest Seminar 1957 Cranbrook-Bloomfield Hills, Michigan
        - General Correspondence 1957 (Box 15)
        - Evaluation, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Seminars (Racine, Wisconsin) 1960-1962 (Box 15)
    - National Recreation Association (Box 15)
    - National Rural Fire Defense Committee 1955 (Box 15)
    - National University Extension Association
      - 1915-1938 (Box 15)
      - 1939-1941 (Box 15)
      - 1942-1943 (Box 15)
      - 1943 (Box 15)
      - 1944-1945, 3 folders (Box 15)
      - 1945-1947 (Box 16)
      - 1948 (Box 16)
      - 1949 (Box 16)
      - 1950 (Box 16)
      - 1951 (Box 16)
      - 1952 (Box 16)
      - 1953 (Box 16)
      - 1954, 5 folders (Box 16)
      - 1955 (Box 16)
      - 1957-1959, 3 folders (Box 16)
      - Committee on the Implications of Atomic Energy 1952-1959 (Box 16)
      - Executive Committee 1951-1953 (Box 16)
      - (Proceedings of the NUEA are available in the University of Michigan Graduate Library) (Box 16)
      - Soop, President 1953-1954 (Box 17)
      - United Nations 1949-1954 (Box 17)
      - Washington Office 1952-1955 (Box 17)
    - Orchestra and Band 1945-1946 (Box 17)
    - Osborn, Stella B. (Mrs. Chase S.) (Box 17)
    - Parent Education-Annual Reports
      - 1939/40-1940/41 (Box 17)
      - 1941-1942, 1942-1943, 1948-1949 (Box 17)
    - President's Office and Regents
      - 1912-1919 (Box 17)
      - 1920-1926 (Box 17)
      - 1927-1934 (Box 17)
      - 1935-1940 (Box 17)
      - 1940-1945 (Box 17)
      - 1945-1959 (Box 17)
    - Provost's Office
      - 1945-1947 (Box 17)
      - 1947-1951 (Box 17)
    - Real Estate Program
      - 1948-1949 (Box 17)
      - 1950-1958 (Box 17)
    - Requests for Lectures 1912
      - Hancock-Kalamazoo (Box 17)
      - Lansing-Midland (Box 17)
      - Milford-Oxford (Box 17)
    - Russell Report 1958 (Miscellaneous correspondence) (Box 18)
    - Secretary's Office
      - 1914-1939 (Box 18)
      - 1942-1948 (Box 18)
    - Special Projects Account 1957-1958 (Box 18)
    - State Universities Association (Box 18)
    - Statistics 1949-1960, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Stevenson, Fred G (Box 18)
    - Television 1950-1953, 5 folders (Box 18)
    - Transportation Education (Box 18)
    - Travel-Staff Memos and Regulation (Box 18)
    - UAW-CIO Labor Institute (Box 18)
    - U.S. Armed Forces Institute, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - United Steelworkers Meeting 1949 (Box 18)
    - University of Michigan Night 1950 (Box 18)
    - University Press (Box 18)
    - University Senate and Council 1935-1937 (Box 18)
    - Veterans Institute (Box 18)
    - Vezanni, Almondo A (Box 18)
    - Vice President Marvin L. Niehuss (Box 18)
    - Vice President Robert P. Briggs (Box 18)
    - Visual Education (Box 18)
    - Wayne University (Box 18)
    - Western Michigan College of Education (Box 18)
    - Williams, Robert L (Box 18)
    - Workers Educational Service, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - YMCA (Box 19)
    - Youth Band (Box 19)
    - Youth Centers (Box 19)
  - Topical Files 1959-1972
    - Academy for Educational Development (Box 19)
    - Adult Education, University Center for
      - 1959-1961, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - 1962-1964, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - 1964-1969, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Aging 1959-1962 (Box 19)
    - American Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities
      - 1961, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - 1962 (Box 19)
      - 1963 (Box 19)
    - American Foundation for Continuing Education (Box 19)
    - Anniversary-50th Extension (Box 19)
    - Arts of Canada 1963 (Box 19)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 20)
    - Audio-Visual Center (U. of M.) (Box 20)
    - Birmingham Alumni Club (Box 20)
    - Broadcasting, Committee on (U. of M.), 8 folders (Box 20)
    - Brown, Nora (Box 20)
    - Cain, Louise (Box 20)
    - Church-Related Colleges (Michigan Association of Church Related Colleges and the University of Michigan) (Box 20)
    - Civil Defense and Disaster
      - Fire Colleges, Fire Universities, and Firemanship Programs (Box 20)
      - Fireman and Electrical Equipment Bulletin (Box 20)
      - Industrial College of the Armed Forces (Box 20)
      - Michigan Office (Box 20)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
      - Training Center, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - HM Door File (Box 20)
      - Leadership Resources, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Universities Committee, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Workshops (Box 20)
    - Clearance (to teach extension courses) (Box 21)
    - Committee on Industrial Cooperation, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Communications Review Committee, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Conference-Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Conferences-Manpower Planning in the 1960s (Box 21)
    - Constitutional Convention 1961-1963 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence Study 1959-1969
      - 1959-1960 (Box 21)
      - 1961 (Box 21)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 21)
      - Steffek Report 1962 (Box 21)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 21)
      - 1964-1969 (Box 21)
    - Course Cancellations, Offerings, and Cooperatives (Box 21)
    - Courses, Co-sponsored (Box 21)
    - Detroit Committee on Foreign Relations (Box 21)
    - Education, Community Adult (Box 22)
    - Education, Community Development (Box 22)
    - Education, Special Program in (Box 22)
    - Education, School of (Box 22)
    - Education, Vocational
      - 1959-1963 (Box 22)
      - 1963-1969 (Box 22)
    - Eley, Lynn, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 22)
    - Engineering, Electrical (Box 22)
    - Engineering Industrial (Box 22)
    - Environment and the Citizen (Box 22)
    - Faculty (Box 22)
    - Fees Committee (U. of M.) (Box 22)
    - Fund for Adult Education (Box 22)
    - Gerontology (Box 22)
    - Governor's Citizens Committee on Higher Education (Box 22)
    - Graduate Professional Program (Box 22)
    - Graduate Program for Teachers (cooperative) (Box 22)
    - Graduate School (U. of M.) (Box 22)
    - Group Centered Programs (Box 22)
    - H-miscellaneous correspondence (Box 22)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 22)
    - Heyns, R. W. (Vice President for Academic Affairs) (Box 22)
    - Higher Education (Box 22)
    - Honor Students, Summer Reading Program (Box 22)
    - I-miscellaneous correspondence (Box 22)
    - Institute for Continuing Legal Education (Box 22)
    - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 22)
    - Illinois, University of (Box 22)
    - Inter-Association (National Adult Education Organizations) (Box 22)
    - Kent State University (Box 22)
    - Law School (U. of M.) (Box 22)
    - Legislation Regarding Extension (Box 22)
    - Legislative Attitude Toward Extension (Box 22)
    - Liverwright, A. A (Box 23)
    - M-miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Medical Assistants Inservice Training Program (Box 23)
    - Michigan Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 23)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council of State College Field Services
      - 1958-1959, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - 1959, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - 1960 (Box 23)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 23)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 23)
      - 1964 (Box 23)
      - 1965, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - 1966 (Box 23)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 23)
      - 1969 (Box 23)
      - Affiliated State Universities Proposal 1968 (Box 24)
      - Citizen's Committee for Higher Education 1964-1965 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous files, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents
      - 1959 (Box 24)
      - 1961 (Box 24)
    - Michigan Council on Economic Education
      - 1964-1965 (Box 24)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 24)
      - Handbook 1965 (Box 24)
    - Michigan Department of Public Instruction
      - 1959-1966 (Box 24)
      - Vocational Education (Box 24)
    - Michigan Library Association (Box 24)
    - Michigan State University (Box 24)
    - Michigan State University-Oakland (Box 24)
    - Michigan Training Laboratory (Box 24)
    - Michigan Week 1960-1964 (Box 24)
    - Michigan Welfare League 1959-1966 (Box 24)
    - Midwest Seminar (Box 24)
    - Minnesota, University of (Box 24)
    - N-miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - National Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities (Box 24)
    - Nelson, Lyle M.-Vice President for University Relations (Box 25)
    - Nelson Associates-Library Needs in Michigan (Box 25)
    - New York University (Box 25)
    - Nursing, School of (U. of M.) (Box 25)
    - O-miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - P-miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - Parent Education Institute
      - 1959-1960 (Box 25)
      - 1961-1966 (Box 25)
    - Pastor's Conference 1959-1964 (Box 25)
    - Project Head Start (Box 25)
    - R-miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - Real Estate 1959-1963 (Box 25)
    - Red Cross Workshop (Box 25)
    - Relations with Public Schools (Box 25)
    - S-miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - Special Projects 1959-1965 (Box 25)
    - Statistics 1958-1961 (Box 25)
    - Stefek, Ralph 1959-1963 (Box 25)
    - Survey Research Center 1959-1962 (Box 25)
    - Theater APA
      - 1962-1963 (Box 25)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 25)
    - U-miscellaneous (Box 26)
    - Vice President for Academic Affairs (Box 26)
    - W-miscellaneous (Box 26)
    - Water Pollution Project 1962-1963 (Box 26)
    - Wayne State University (Box 26)
    - White House Commission on Aging 1958-1961 (Box 26)
    - Williams, Robert L.-Committee on University-School Relations (Box 26)
    - Wisconsin, University of (Box 26)
  - Topical Files circa 1936-1980
    The Topical File, ca. 1936-1980 in part continues the subjects listed in the 1982 accession. The most significant file is the "Evaluation and Planning Project." This was a university-wide project begun in 1973 in response to the budget crisis of the 1970s. The project was conducted in three phases: I) articulation of unit objectives and operations implications; II) evaluation of operations in light of objectives described in phase I; and III) exploration of directions and alternative courses of action. The file includes a number of internal and external reports and studies, questionnaires, and statistics on enrollment, funding and expenses. It provides an interesting look at the Extension Service's goals and objectives and the range of its programs in the early 1970s. Other significant files include the High School Correspondence Studies Reports, Community College Advisory Committee, the Rackham Building (Detroit) anniversaries, and Washtenaw Community College.
    - Atomic/Space/Human Race Discussion Groups 1959-1960 (Box 50)
    - Birmingham Center for Continuing Education, Feasibility Study 1979 (Box 50)
    - Community Based Bachelor of Science in Nursing Program 1974-1980 (Box 50)
    - Community Colleges (Box 51)
      - Advisory Committee Minutes
        - 1973-1977 (Box 51)
        - 1978-1980 (Box 51)
      - Banfield "Articulation" Studies 1973-1977 (Box 51)
    - Conference Center circa 1956-1960, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Correspondence Studies
      - Histories, Reports etc. circa 1936-1965, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - (Coordinating Council for Continuing Higher Education, see box 62) (Box 51)
    - Detroit Association for Adult Education 1942-1945 (Box 51)
    - Division of Adult Education
      - 1960 (Box 51)
      - 1961
        - January-May (Box 51)
        - June-Sept (Box 51)
        - October-Dec (Box 51)
        - 1962 January-June (Box 51)
      - University Center for Adult Education 1957-1962 (Box 51)
    - Engineering 1960-1963 (Box 51)
    - Evaluation and Planning Project
      - Phase I, 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Phase II and III (Box 51)
    - Great Books Program 1946-1947 (Box 51)
    - High School Correspondence Studies Reports (Valois Reports) 1960-1961, 3 folders (Box 51)
    - International Conference on University Adult Education Study Tour 1965 (Box 51)
    - "Life & Times of Frank and Beatrice Spotts" by Frank Spotts, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Rackham Building (Detroit) (Box 52)
      - 20th Anniversary 1962 (Box 52)
      - 25th Anniversary 1967 (Box 52)
    - School of Natural Resources
      - International Parks Seminar 1974-1981 (Box 52)
      - Sea Grant Program 1969-1976 (Box 52)
    - UM-Flint and UM-Dearborn (Box 52)
    - Washtenaw Community College
      - "Citizens Survey of Washtenaw County Community College Possibilities," 1963 (Box 52)
      - Enrichment Programs 1974-1980 (Box 52)
  - Topical Files 1950-1994, 1977-1984
    Topical Files, 1950-1994 contain background and planning information on the various extension services centers around the state of Michigan, individual courses and programs, as well as materials related to the Extension Service's history, objectives and self-assessment. General histories are included as well as information on specific school and college offerings. The bulk of these records are from the 1970s and early 1980s.
    - Academic Interlude Program 1978 (Box 58)
    - Accreditation Review 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - Advisory Committee on Extension Activity (includes Review) 1981-1983 (Box 58)
    - Algonquin Course 1981-1982 (Box 58)
    - American Culture 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - Ann Arbor 1978-1981 (Box 58)
    - Ann Arbor Classes Since 1930, 1950 (Box 58)
    - Annual Report (includes background material) 1978/79, 1979 (Box 58)
    - Anthropology 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - Architecture 1980-1981 (Box 58)
    - Art 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - Berlin, Lawrence 1976-1978 (Box 58)
    - Center for Near-Eastern and North African Studies 1980-1981 (Box 58)
    - Certificate Programs, circa 1978 (Box 58)
    - China 1980-1983 (Box 58)
    - Communications Office 1978-1981 (Box 58)
    - Continuing Education Unit 1970-1973 (Box 58)
    - Credit By Examination 1973-1976 (Box 58)
    - Credit Courses (General)
      - APC Policy Issues 1979-1980 (Box 58)
      - Course Ideas 1978-1980 (Box 58)
      - Student Course Evaluations, circa 1978 (Box 58)
    - Credit Course Programs
      - Director 1974-1978 (Box 58)
      - Assistant Director 1979 (Box 58)
      - Regional Center Operating Policies 1979 (Box 58)
      - Credit Survey 1980 (Box 58)
    - CREES (Center for Russian and Eastern European Studies) 1980 (Box 58)
    - Dearborn
      - General 1979 (Box 58)
      - Birmingham Center 1978-1979 (Box 58)
      - English 1977-1979 (Box 58)
    - Detroit
      - General 1978-1980 (Box 58)
      - Program in American Culture 1978-1980 (Box 58)
    - Dow Chemical (Midland) 1958-1980 (Box 58)
    - Education
      - General 1977-1992, 3 folders (Box 58)
      - Master of Arts Programs, circa 1978 (Box 58)
      - Occupational Education 1976-1980 (Box 58)
      - School of Education 1973-1983 (Box 58)
      - Special Course Descriptions 1978-1981 (Box 58)
      - UM Dearborn 1978-1979 (Box 58)
    - Egypt 1981 (Box 58)
    - Engineering
      - General 1975-1987 (Box 58)
      - Chemical Engineering (Saginaw) 1977-1980 (Box 58)
      - Civil Engineering 1978 (Box 58)
      - Engineering Humanities 1979-1980 (Box 58)
      - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Flint) 1978-1980 (Box 58)
      - Jackson 1978-1979 (Box 58)
      - Special Course Descriptions 1980 (Box 58)
    - English 1980 (Box 58)
    - Faculty Compensation, 1973-c.1979 (Box 58)
    - Flint
      - Flint-Genesee Inter-University Workshop 1978-1979 (Box 58)
      - Miscellaneous 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - GSTA Stipend 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - Graduate Professional Studies 1960-1971, 5 folders (Box 58)
    - Grand Rapids
      - Art 1978-1979 (Box 58)
      - Credit Programming 1979-1981 (Box 58)
      - English 1977-1981 (Box 58)
      - General 1978-1980 (Box 58)
      - Kent Inter-University Workshop 1978-1980 (Box 58)
    - History
      - Detroit Center 1963 (Box 59)
      - Histories and Related Materials 1932-1983, 3 folders (Box 59)
      - Upper Peninsula Office 1970 (Box 59)
    - History of Art 1979-1981 (Box 59)
    - Program for Human Resource Development 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Independent Study 1973-1975 (Box 59)
    - Independent Television Corp. Contract 1973 (Box 59)
    - Industry/Business 1979-1980 (Box 59)
    - Institute of Gerontology 1972-1984, 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Library Science
      - General 1976-1982 (Box 59)
      - Proposal 1979 (Box 59)
    - Institute for the Study of Mental Retardation 1969-1970 (Box 59)
    - Milan Staff Project 1965-1968 (Box 59)
    - Music
      - General 1977-1982, 1994, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - CBDNA Winter 1981 Credit Course 1980-1981 (Box 59)
      - School of Music 1977-1979 (Box 59)
      - Special Course Descriptions 1981 (Box 59)
    - Natural Resources 1976-1987, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Noncredit Courses Program Agreement 1983 (Box 59)
    - Nursing
      - 1974-1992, 5 folders (Box 59)
      - Pamphlets 1975-1994 (Box 59)
    - Pharmacy 1980-1981 (Box 59)
    - Political Science 1978-1980 (Box 59)
    - Psychology
      - General 1978-1982 (Box 59)
      - Special Course Descriptions 1979-1981 (Box 59)
    - Public Health
      - General 1977-1985 (Box 59)
      - Surveys and Reports 1978-1979 (Box 59)
    - Rackham Graduate School 1975-1977 (Box 59)
    - Saginaw 1979-1980 (Box 59)
    - Social Work
      - General 1970-1995, 3 folders (Box 59)
      - Continuing Education and Extension Committee 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Cooperative Program Proposal 1970-1977 (Box 58)
      - Credit Courses 1978-1980 (Box 58)
      - Proposal for a National Child Welfare Training Center 1979 (Box 58)
      - Proposal for a Region V Adoption Resource Center 1979 (Box 58)
      - Special Course Descriptions 1980-1981 (Box 58)
      - Stipend Proposals 1968-1973 (Box 58)
    - Sociology 1979-1981 (Box 58)
    - Wayne County Inter-University Workshop 1972-1981, 3 folders (Box 58)
- Central Office Files
  The Central Office Files consist of area office records. These files contain the records of the Detroit, Flint, Grand Rapids, Saginaw, Traverse City, and Upper Peninsula offices as well as files relating to Extension Service activities in other Michigan cities. The records concerning the Detroit office contain materials from the Ann Arbor central office and files from the Rackham Educational Memorial Building in Detroit, which have been interfiled.
  - Area Office Records
    - All Center Course Programs
      - 1934-1948 (Box 26)
      - 1949-1959 (Box 26)
    - Ann Arbor
      - 1929-1942 (Box 26)
      - 1950-1958 (Box 26)
      - 1959-1964 (Box 26)
    - Battle Creek 1933-1968 (Box 26)
    - Dearborn (Box 26)
    - Detroit
      - Academic Interlude 1977-1978 (Box 27)
      - Age of Opportunity 1955-1960, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Annual Reports
        - 1945/1946-1954/1955 (Box 27)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 27)
        - 1964/1965-1976/1977- 1978-1979 (Box 27)
      - Area Center
        - 1931-1949 (Box 27)
        - 1950-1962 (Box 27)
      - Auditorium Rental Procedures (Box 27)
      - Course Program History 1963 (Box 27)
      - Cumulative Reports 1956-1981 (Box 27)
      - Discrimination-Arnold D. Law (Box 27)
      - Engineering Society of Detroit 1954-1955 (Box 27)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 27)
      - Minutes, Staff Meetings 1952-1958 (Box 27)
      - Program of Technical Courses 1956 (Box 27)
      - Project Extension, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Rackham Building (Box 27)
      - Registration
        - 1932/33-1936/37 (Box 27)
        - 1948/49-1951/52 (Box 27)
        - 1952/53-1956/57 (Box 27)
        - 1957/58-1959/60 (Box 27)
      - Reports
        - 1938-1942 (Box 27)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 27)
        - 1960 (Box 27)
        - 1963 (Box 27)
      - Robert Schultz Correspondence 1979-1982 (Box 27)
      - Semester Registration, 1976/1977- 1980-1981 (Box 28)
      - Semester Reports
        - 1945/1946- 1948-1949 (Box 28)
        - 1949/1950-1954/1955 (Box 28)
        - 1955/1956-1959/1960 (Box 28)
        - 1960/1961-1964/1965 (Box 28)
        - 1965/1966-1968/1969 (Box 28)
        - 1969/1970-1974/1975 (Box 28)
      - Semester Summaries
        - 1950/1951-1958/1959 (Box 28)
        - 1959/1960-1964/1965 (Box 28)
        - 1975/1976-1981/1982 (Box 28)
      - Special Projects 1943-1944 (Box 28)
      - Staff 1944-1945 (Box 28)
      - Statistics
        - 1944-1947 (Box 28)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 28)
      - Summer Session Reports
        - 1945-1948 (Box 28)
        - 1949-1954 (Box 28)
        - 1955-1959 (Box 28)
        - 1950-1964 (Box 28)
      - Surveys 1945-1961 (Box 28)
      - University Center for Adult Education
        - Five Year Plan 1966-1971 (Box 28)
        - History (Box 28)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
      - University Cultural Center Association (Box 28)
      - Workers Educational Service 1944-1948, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Adult Education Association 1943-1944 (Box 52)
      - C.A. Fisher-E.J. Soop Correspondence 1936-1942 (Box 52)
      - Correspondence circa 1936-1943, 3 folders (Box 52)